Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the Tim
Dylan Show. Thank you guys so much for
watching the special on Netflix. I'm
your mother. We are, as of the recording
of this
show, number eight right now on Netflix
behind Love on the
Spectrum. That is a feel-good
show. Everybody wants all different
types of people to find love. And I
almost feel like because RFK, friend of
the show, made some pointed
comments about our autistic brothers and
sisters whom we love, appreciate, and
cherish. And he said that autism
destroys families and children and none
of them will use a toilet. And I don't
think he meant it to come off the way he
did. I know many autistic people who use
toilets and that's
nice. But I think that the Love on the
Spectrum show, it's like people are
there's a moment of defiance people are
having watching Love on the Spectrum
going, "We're going to watch
it."
Okay? Because they're going to the
Netflix top 10. You have Black Mirror,
which is completely falling apart. This
is what people do in their house. They
go to the Netflix top 10. They go, "What
is this?" The Netflix top 10 is always
relatively the
same. It is a
romcom. It is a true
crime. It is a show from like Norway or
one of this the countries about like
Norse mythology or something. It's like
some fun fantasy show. Um and then you
have a popular reality show, A Love is
Blind, The Circle, Love on the Spectrum.
Then you maybe have a
comedian, okay? And then you have a a
show like a Young Sheldon, a network
show that Netflix
purchased. And these are the choices.
And people are like, "Hey
man, what are we going to do here? What
are we going to watch?" And I think
there are people right now because again
they're sensitive about maybe some of
the comments that were made about the
autistic community and all of RFK is
trying to say is let's figure out why
this is
happening.
Not like I don't think he's saying like
hey if someone's autistic let's put him
in the
shed. That's not what's happening. I
don't I'm not getting that. That's not
what I'm
getting. But there are people that feel
like the tenor of his comments are if
someone's autistic, let's take them out
in the
woods. That's not what's hap that's not
what I'm getting from it. I'm getting he
wants to figure out what's going on. But
I think a lot of people are going this
Love on the Spectrum show is actually a
beautiful
show because we're seeing we're this is
the way we
support that beautiful community and I
have no problem. I'm just saying let's
also watch my thing because people are
enjoying
it and let's try to move it up the ranks
here. That's all I'm saying.
I think some of RFK's comments, they
landed sometimes a comment can land
wrong when he went on that whole thing
where he's like, "Autism destroys our
most precious resource. Our children,
these children will never go on a date.
They will never use a toilet on their
own. They will never go sledding down a
hill. They will never have a goldfish.
They will never pet a dog in a way that
doesn't make you nervous.
They will never swing from a tree while
sitting on a
rope. They will never fly a plane and
crash in the Atlantic Ocean. They will
never get addicted to heroin. They will
never be assassinated by the Central
Intelligence Agency. One of the hardest
things about growing up with severe
autism is you will not be assassinated
by the Central Intelligence Agency.
Watch the special. It's actually nice.
And now I I want to text you this
because by the way, this guy that they
sent to El Salvador. Now I don't They're
saying it was a mistake. I don't know
what's going on here. I'm just going to
tell you this guy is d was dressed
exactly like me. Take a look at this. I
just texted you a photo. I want you to
bring this photo up and I want you to
bring the f the uh where I was with
Megan Kelly and I want you to tell this
guy his name is Kilmar. Is that the best
name to have? No, I mean literally
Kilmar. Kilmar Abrego Garcia. He was
deported to El Salvador from
Maryland after he was accused of being a
member of MS13. And this is part of the
Trump administration's new initiative to
get rid of illegal gang members.
However, a lot of people are saying this
guy wasn't a gang member and they're
sending all of these people to this is
Salv this prison in El Salvador run by
Boulli who has you know built this like
supermax prison that a lot of human
rights groups don't
love and he took all these MS-13
gangsters and he put them in it and this
guy was shipped to that prison.
And he look I mean he's dressing exactly
like me. This guy if you pull up this
photo I just saying this is the craziest
thing. What is going
on? This guy now get me on Megan
Kelly. This
guy he's visiting with a senator. A
senator from Maryland went down there to
go see him. this prison in I mean what
is h that is the same drip literally now
go back to
him now me
again now
him he's in better shape because that
prison they get you into better
shape
now he had a
tattoo. Now, supposedly he's saying his
tattoo was autism
awareness. Look this up. But other
people thought, and by other people I
mean like ice. They thought it was an
MS13, too. I mean a MS-13
tattoo. A
tattoo. So, this guy apparently has an
autism awareness tattoo.
this is
what people are
saying. And I don't know, maybe that's
true. I will say at the risk it does
seem
odd
that he had an autism awareness tattoo.
That's all. I'm not saying that
it's completely impossible. It's very
possible. Is this his tattoo? Yeah,
that's it's a that's a lion. That's just
a
lion. We didn't deport him for having a
lion,
right? Supposedly, his
tattoo is indicative of the fact that he
was a member of the MS13 gang. Is that
it? Oh, it's an image on his left hand.
see about the autism awareness thing
because that's what people are claiming
that he has. They're saying that he's
got like he cares a lot about autism.
It's not
MS-13. And maybe that's correct. I don't
know. Asylum seeker sent to Salvador and
mega prison over autism awareness
tattoo. family says, "Oh, this is maybe
another
guy. This is another
guy. Oh, this is a Venezuelan migrant
who was living in Texas and he was
sent to El Salvador because of an autism
awareness. Let show him cuz he had an
autistic brother so he got an autism
awareness tattoo." Does that seem I'm
asking I don't want I I don't want to
start any problems. Is that it?
Yeah.
Okay.
Okay. What is the gang that that looks
like? Like I'm asking like what is the
gang? What is the Is there a gang that
has that like gay symbol?
What gang did they think he was in? The
trend to Aagua. I think they That's the
uh Yeah, that's the Venezuelan gang that
there's a lot of them in New York or
was. He said, "But I have my asylum. I
have the asylum papers here with
me." And the people said, "No, you're
going to jail because you have a
tattoo."
So, was that the only evidence? Here's
the thing.
Obviously, most people are for deporting
violent criminals. Obviously, some
people aren't. They're insane, right?
They just don't
care. His friends and family said he was
told by immigration authorities that the
tattoo was proof he belonged to the
Venezuelan gang, Trendiagua. Can you get
up a Trendi Aua tattoo and let's compare
it because maybe they're
similar? I don't know.
They don't look
similar. They're trying to get rid of
gang members and it's hard because they
got to go through all their
tattoos. They got to go through the
tattoos of people here illegally and and
and it's not easy. And unfortunately, I
think people are getting
deported because they have a tattoo, but
it's not a gang
tattoo. This is all pretty
sloppy. We all want violent criminals.
Yeah. None of them have a None of those
guys have
a a rainbow ribbon
tattoo. That doesn't even look like a
dangerous tattoo. Get that guy's tattoo
up again. That doesn't even look That
guy. I feel
like that's is that if that's a gang,
you want that gang here. That looks like
a gang that goes and like helps kids
with cancer. That doesn't seem like a
dangerous gang. That seems like they
clean up the street or
something. Now, I don't know. Maybe that
is a
gang, but it's I mean, you want to
rethink the ink if that's a gang. So I
think now obviously these gentlemen not
we don't need them. They should go. A
lot of them should go. The trend AWA has
got to go. MS-13 has to go. But they
sent a gay hair stylist somewhere.
That's not good. He He wasn't in a gang.
This guy wasn't in a gang. This other
guy smacked his wife around. The guy
from Maryland. This guy Kilmore Abrego
Garcia. But Abrego Garcia was, I think,
talking to MS-13 gang members. Go to an
article
about Garcia because he was picked up.
There there were informants that said he
was an MSRT. And maybe that isn't true.
Maybe they're
lying about it. His wife filed a
protective order against him in
2021, but now she came out and said,
"Hey, he's a pretty good guy." Okay,
this is like every woman who's ever
filed a protective order. But I'm not
saying, by the way, that he should be
condemned for a protective order. I'm
just saying she did accuse him of of
violence. She did accuse him of
attacking
her. And other people have claimed that
he was in
MS-13. I don't know what his job was.
Like I the real story Kilmar Abbrego
Garcia is an MS-13 gang member with a
history of violence. So this is from
Homeland Security. So, I don't know if
you want to believe this or not. Make
this bigger. You take this with a grain
of salt. I'm not endorsing
this. This is what people are saying.
When he was arrested, he was found with
rolls of cash and drugs. He was arrested
with two other members of MS-13. Now, by
the way, whether this guy is guilty or
not, I do think there is a problem
sending people to a Venice to a El
Salvadoran prison without any due
process. I get it.
Um, I think that is opens the door to a
big problem. But this particular dude, I
don't
know. I don't know if he might be he
might not be the poster boy for this,
you know, like he might not be the guy
to defend, but I don't know. But you got
to defend the principle, right? I think
the principle is but what do you do?
Here's the thing. If you have violent
gang members that come to the country
and you catch them, there's got to be
some due process. That's what America's
based on. But I don't think you have to
keep them here and keep them in taxpayer
funded jails. Like you can deport them.
I don't know if you necessarily send
them to some prison in El Salvador. So
they're saying when this guy was
arrested, he was wearing a sweatshirt
with rolls of money covering the ears,
mouth, and eyes of presidents on various
currency denominations. This is known as
an MS-13 gang se symbol of see no evil,
hear no evil, say no
evil. Two judges found that he was a
member of MS-13. That finding has not
been disturbed. Intelligence reports
found that he was involved in human
trafficking. Here is an illegal alien
from El Salvador. The subject freely
admitted being citizen and national of
El Salvador by birth and that they were
present in the United States. legally
the subject were not in possession of
any immigration documents that would
allow them to be in or remain in the
United States legally. He claimed fear
of being returned to El Salvador because
he would be persecuted by MS13's rival
gang Barriio
18. Jennifer Vasquez Garcia's wife
petitioned for an order of protection
against him. She claimed he punched her,
scratched her, ripped off her shirt, and
bruised her. They include the protective
order. But she did come out and say,
"Listen, I took out a protective order
cuz I was in a previous relationship
with someone
who was abusive and I was just trying to
be careful." Um, get her up. She does
talk about this case. She is unhappy
that he was sent away.
If you're running a business, you know
that every time you miss a call, you're
leaving money on the table. When every
conversation matters with a customer,
you need a phone system that keeps you
up and keeps you connected. You got to
stay
connected. You need open
phone. I have friends, whether they're
in real estate, they're plumbers or
electricians, they're in a customer
service position where they need they
need to service a customer base and they
need to grow it. Every missed call is
money that you're not getting. In
today's fast-moving world, your team
needs to stay connected to your
customers without missed messages,
communication silos, or slow phone
systems. A flexible and efficient
business phone system isn't just nice to
have. It's essential to succeed. Enter
Open Phone. It's the number one business
phone system that streamlines and scales
your customer communications. It works
through an app on your phone or
computer, so no more carrying two phones
or using a landline. With Open Phone,
your team can share one number and
collaborate on customer calls and texts
like a shared
inbox. Even better, Open Phone is
offering my listeners 20% off your first
six months at
openphone.com/tim. That's openphone.com.
o pen
ph.comim. And if you have existing
numbers with another service, open phone
will port them over at no extra charge.
Open phone, no miss calls, no missed
customers. When when something like this
happens and you have a guy who has a
very
questionable, you know,
history
and there's a very good
chance that he was involved
in some type of, let's say, [__]
I do think that it is important to cross
your tees and dot your
eyes and make sure you have a solid case
against him so that you don't turn him
into a folk hero if he not need not be
one. You know, like the other guy with
the tattoo I totally get. He's got a
tattoo for his autistic brother and
they're like, "Bro, you're in the gang."
What if he's in the gang? What if his
autistic brother runs the gang? Like, we
don't know what's No one knows what's
going on. Let's watch this woman. This
is the wife of Kilar Abrego Garcia, who
was deported to Central America from
Maryland after being accused of being in
uh MS-13. Here is his wife speaking.
There's a lot of people here. They want
him back.
Good afternoon. Good afternoon. My name
is Jennifer. Good to meet you. I am
Kilmer's wife. Hello. He is a father, a
son, a brother, and a proud member of
CASA and smart union member who has
dedicated his himself to make our
family's American dream reality. It
would be it would be funny if she said
he's a proud member of
MS-13 and then she went, "Shit." She
turned around and they go, "Keep going."
She goes, "And he is a proud member of
MS." Shh. No, no, no, no, no. Keep
going. Keep going. He's not. They go,
"He's not at
MS-13." All right, let's let's listen to
her. I don't know. I didn't know he was
in all these unions and
um they said she he was in Casa or Cava.
He's in a Cava. My my my friend my
cousin knew a girl named Demetri. They
met in rehab in Delray Beach. She was in
a Cava. Cava is like
u it's like a a drug people get into.
You know what cava is? I think it's like
a type of drink. It's a drink, but
people get really start getting whacked
out on it and it's like it's a way to
replace like opium. But that's not what
she means. I think she said casa, which
means house. Continue.
That dream was shattered on March 12th
when he was abducted and disappeared by
the United States government in front of
our 5-year-old
child. Today is 34 days of after his
disappearance and I stand before you
filled with
spirit that refuses to bring
down. I will not stop fighting. That's
not Hold
on. That's not grammatically correct
when she said spirit that refuses to
bring
down. I'm trying to think of another way
she could have said that. I'm standing
here with spirit that will not
be I'm standing here with a spirit that
is
ferocious. And and you know what I
mean? Continue. see my husband
alive. Kilmar, if you can hear
me, stay
strong. God hasn't forgotten about
you. Our childrens are
asking when will you come
home? And I pray for the day I tell them
the time and date that you'll return.
Hold on for a minute. I don't know. It's
hard to know here what's going
on. Is this a good
guy or is this guy a
problem? And I don't know. And this is
going to be one of those things where
they go, "Podcasters talk without the
facts. You don't have the
facts. Who are you to influence?" I
said, "I don't know." Nine
times. I said, "I don't know." And
they're going to say that. They're going
to go, "Well, you're talking about it."
Yeah, everyone's talking about it. We're
all talking about it. That doesn't mean
I'm I'm not condemning this man. I
really don't know. I feel for this
woman, but this guy might have been a
really bad guy that was in a gang and he
might have told her that he wasn't. Or
she might know he was and he might have
been bringing in
money doing that. or this is a complete
case of like mistaken
identity and they deported this guy
without any due process and this is a
guy that may have had some trouble but
was for the most part a law-abiding
citizen. That's not
what the government is
contending. Let's keep listening to
uh his wife. Do you know her name?
Jennifer Vasquez, I believe.
Good job. Let's keep listening to
Jennifer Vasquez and see. I don't know.
We're We're looking for
clues. I'm looking
for
clues. I'm looking at this big woman
next to her two to the right, and I'm
looking at her earring. She's got a
chunky earring there, like a green
earring.
Now, this thing, Casa, she's a member of
two. This CASA on the shirt. I don't
know what this is, but I'm I'm paying
attention to all of this. Keep going
here. Let's see if there's any tells.
Like story wars. If someone's lying,
they have a tell. Let's see if there are
any tells. She's looking down a lot, but
I also think that's just because this is
not her first language. So, in fairness,
I think she's reading
this. Go.
As we continue through Holy Week, my
heart Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Holy Week, invoking Holy
Week seems a little
sus. There's something
about saying as we go through Holy
Week that makes me
think that there's a lot of guns and
drugs in her
house, but I could be wrong. Again,
don't come to me. Don't tell me I'm
being irresponsible. I'm merely watching
this as a citizen of our country trying
to figure out what's going on. I thought
the Holy Week thing a little odd.
Continue. As we continue through Holy
Week, my heart aches for my
husband. Who should I had been here
leading our Easter
prayers? Instead, I find myself pleading
with the Trump administration and the
Boulli
administration to stop playing political
games with the life of
Kilmer. Our family is torn
apart during this scary time and our
childrens miss their dad so much.
Despite the challenges we continue to
face with the US and the Salvadorian
government still, I hope that the
strength of faith and the resilience
within us will keep us standing after
all the punches we cons we continue to
receive. A lot of violent language after
all the punches we continue to receive.
A lot of violent language. Kind of
interesting. These are just notes I'm
taking in my head. After all the times
they try to slit our
throat, they try to they try to they
they try to kill us, you know, after all
the times they try to pistol whip us, we
still I'm like, wait a minute. Cuz I'm
just wonder I'm trying to trying to
ascertain what what's going on here.
Keep keep going. And I could be I could
listen, I'm not the judge in the jury.
go. Our ability to fight back against
these governments are testimonies to the
spirit of fight and restraint that God
has given us. We will continue standing
strong and we will never give up on you,
Kilmar.
Okay, that's nice.
Even though my heart is
heavy, I find hope and strength in those
around
me. I felt an overwhelming
support from our communities. Wait a
minute. Hold on. Hold
on. Community. Then she said our
brothers. She's getting close maybe to
revealing something here. We're all
We're at the edge of our seat here. Be
very careful here. Now, the woman in the
back looks nervous. Look at the woman in
the back. She looks a little nervous.
She might be about to give away the
game. Let's run it back a few seconds.
Let's see. She's She's appealing now to
her community and her brothers. What
does that mean? Let's see. We don't
know. Let's go support from our
communities, our brothers and sisters
from CASA, leaders and members from
SMRT. Our faith in Ali communities who
continue to stand with us. Yes. And I
pray to MS3 that the same community
strengthen has lifted me flows through
those judges
supporting her to bend the power towards
justice. And even though Kilmore cannot
earn, his friends have told me that I
will get a percentage of the money that
he was making on the street until he is
back to make things
right. I will be made whole again when
he is
back in the States. No, I don't know.
Get it out of here. I don't know. And
people are going to be angry with me.
They're going to say I'm being
insensitive. I just don't know. I don't
I don't know. Let's watch Carolyn Lev.
She's a little bit of a psychopath, but
maybe she's got the goods. We don't
know. She's a She's got the energy of um
of a of a a a woman who would uh drown a
cat. But let's She
does while it was screaming like there.
So, let's just see what Carolyn Levit
here. Interesting. Woman has the energy
of a woman who would uh put a cat's head
under the water and while its body
fought like all hell for a gasp of air,
she would keep it under the water.
Carolyn Levit, the White House.
Basic fact that he was illegally inside
our country and had a lawful deportation
order made him subject to removal back
to his home country of El Salvador. And
if he ever ends up back in the United
States, he would immediately be deported
again. Nothing will change the fact that
Obago Garcia will never be a Maryland
father. He will never live in the United
States of America again. And the United
States Supreme Court ruled unanimously
that the president of the United States
and the Secretary of State could not be
compelled to forcibly retrieve this
citizen of El Salvador who is currently
locked up in a maximum security prison
in his home country.
Yeah, I mean again I understand people
being uncomfortable with this and I
would say just like I criticize some of
the deportations that are happening
because of the campus
protests. I think I have no problem with
gang members being deported. I even
think some people that came here that
are lawful or good people but came here
in the last four
years, Biden let in 10 million people.
Not all of them are going to be able to
stay. We probably just can't assimilate
all of them into this country at this
point. That's something that's pretty
wellnown. Most Americans want
illegal immigration to stop and they
also want people that, you know, maybe
that have not lived here for many, many
years lawfully, but people that are
newly
here to go. I don't know if this guy was
arrested with drugs and cash on him. I
mean, cash is not illegal, but drugs are
illegal. Do we know what drugs he was
arrested with? Do we know that? Do we
have
anything? Do we have
anything on
that? It's not like I
have the power to do anything
anyway. I wonder what he was arrested
with. Maybe he wasn't arrested with
drugs, but Homeland Security is
claiming that when he was
arrested, he was arrested
with drugs.
Right. That's what they're
saying. He was found with rolls of cash
and drugs. I'd like to know what
drugs. Keep Keep Make this bigger. Make
it bigger.
On 328 2019 at approximately blank,
detective blank of the Heightsville city
police observed four individuals
loitering in the park lot of a Home
Depot at 330 to1 East West Highway in
Hitzville, Maryland. As he approached
the individuals, two of the individuals
reached into their waistbands and
discarded several unknown items under a
parked vehicle. All of the four
individuals are stopped by Hyetszville.
Officer Blank immediately
recognized Cresianne Hernandez Romero
aka Bimbo as a member of the MS13 Sailor
Click, which doesn't seem terrible, the
Sailor's Click. Two small plastic
bottles containing marijuana was located
on scene. All four individuals are
transported back to district for
interviews.
member of the Prince George's County
gang. MS-13 intelligence squad have
uncountered Christian Hernandez Romero
on multiple occasions. He has extensive
criminal
history. Okay. And then there's this
other guy,
Dominguez. Officers also interviewed
Joseé Glammo Dominguez. During the
interview, officers observe tattoos of
skulls covering their eyes. Da da da da
da
da. So, this guy's got some MS-13
tattoos. Officers then interviewed Kilar
Armando Abrego Garcia. During the
interview, officers, and Do we have
anything more? During the interview,
officers observed he was wearing the
Chicago Bulls hat and a hoodie with the
rolls of money, which we talked about.
Officers know each clo that clothing to
be indicative of Hispanic gang culture.
That's a little loose to be honest. The
meaning of the clothing is to represent
something senovil senovil. Okay, so it's
just clothing.
The confidential source further advised
that he
is a member of MS-13. So, they had
somebody who said he's an active member
of
MS-13.
Um, but I don't think this guy was
charged with a crime. I believe this is
where you run into an issue. They were
unable to charge him with a crime. He
was hanging out with some MS-13 guys.
They had
drugs. They all looked sus. The cops
went over there in the Home Depot
parking lot. Found drugs, found cash.
These guys had extensive criminal
histories. This guy uh Garcia is with
them. They interview him. He's dressed
kind of in the way that a lot of gang
members would dress, but he doesn't they
don't charge him with a crime from what
I'm seeing
here.
Um, the wife who was just on camera was
the one who petitioned for the order of
protection and she claimed that he
attacked her physically but has now
walked that back in the press and said
that she was doing that as a precaution.
Um, so this is as much as we really know
here. This is the story is de is
developing, but this is the story. This
is what we got. So here's the thing. In
a court petition, Vasquez describes
multiple incidents over the course of
several days in 2021. Well, this is peak
pandemic and tempers are
hot. They're flaring. They're actually
really, really flaring. I was
getting I was in a war with my roommate
and she's a very talented comedian who
wears a wig and we would argue because
she would live stream in the tub. 2021
was a dark
time. In one case, Vasquez wrote that
ago Garcia got angry with her at a gas
station, insulted her, and drove very
fast. Okay, that one I don't care about,
[__] That is not why you file a
report. Okay. Days later, Vasquez
alleges Abrago Garcia yelled at her to
turn off her laptop. Understandable. And
when she said she wasn't tired, she said
he got angry and threw her laptop on the
floor. It's destruction of property. She
alleged she pushed him off her and then
he punched her, scratching on my left
eye, left me
bleeding. Later that day, Abrego Garcia
allegedly tore off Vasquez's shorts and
shirt and grabbed me by the arm when she
ran away, leaving a mark on her left
arm. the following morning after he
allegedly didn't give her a set of car
keys. She called an Uber for her and the
kids because she was quote scared of him
and afraid to be close to him. I have
multiple photos, videos of how violent
he can be and all the bruises he has
left me. This is what she wrote in the
petition. The case, however, was
dismissed in June 2021 after Vasquez
failed to appear for final hearing. This
happens all the time.
If it is a legitimate case of abuse, a
lot of women do not follow through with
it. They're in love with a guy who is a
bad
dude. I'm just trying to get all this
information. The summer is coming, guys.
You want to be ready when she needs it.
Get your first month of Bluetooth free.
Great sex is a few clicks away. Sign up
at bluech.com. Consult with one of their
licensed medical providers. And once
you're approved, you'll receive your
prescription within days. Bluetooth
tablets are made in the USA and prepared
and shipped directly to your door. The
best part, it's all done online. That
means no visits to the doctor's office,
no awkward conversations, and no waiting
in line at the pharmacy. I'm telling you
right now, make life easier by getting
harder and discovered your options at
Bluetooth.com. And we've got a special
deal for our listeners. Try your first
month of Bluetooth free when you use
promo code TD. Just pay $5 shipping.
That's promo code TD. Visit bluechw.com
for more details and important safety
information. I mean, it's so important
right now to have Bluetooth. Made in the
USA. Made in the USA. They're made in
the USA. No tariff needed here. Visit
bluetw.com for more details and
important safety information. We thank
Blu for sponsoring the
podcast. I'm doing a bunch of fun comedy
podcasts like Story Wars and Legionist
Gangs, all that stuff.
Rogan, but I'm also doing these news
shows and I go to like Fox and all these
channels and you know, cable news is in
a weird position. I mean, they can
barely get these kids are so sweet, the
interns or who's ever working
there. I mean, they can barely get the
head the the earpiece in and the the
mics don't work and the cameras barely
work. And by the way, I did an hour with
El Reeves at CNN, released that
interview. It's a good interview and
release the hour. Do not edit that. They
said they were going to edit it. If you
edit it and put a small chunk of it on
your network, put the full hour. We
spoke for about an hour, right? Maybe
even
longer. Release the full interview. It's
a great interview. But I'll tell you
right now, she told me a lot of people
refuse to go on CNN. They're going to
edit this. And the reason that a lot of
people refuse to go on CNN is because
they're going to edit my
interview instead of releasing it in
full online. I know it's a cable
network. You can't put it all on cable,
but I'm telling you right now, you
should release the full
interview on YouTube, on
CNN.com. Let people make their own
decisions. the full unedited interview
from the moment I sit down in the chair
until we say
goodbye. That full interview should be
out. If you release Now, my producer was
not able to come in the CNN room because
I thought I was going in there for 10
minutes like the rest of these where you
go in, it's quick, you know, they go,
"What about cancel culture?" And the
woke left, the woke cancelling cancel
culture. Wokedians can't say anything
anymore. Why can't you? And then I go,
"Yeah, I mean, it's, you know, I'm I'm
just talking and you know, it's it's out
there people. You know, what are you
gonna I get it. This is the narrative.
This is the thing. Whatever. It's fine.
I did all in and I love those guys. We
had a lot of fun. They're talking about
Nvidia chips being backdoored through
fake companies in Bhutan to China.
That's what I'm into. I don't want to
talk about cancel culture. I'm bored. I
want to hear Chimath talk about chips in
Bhutan.
was a lot of fun. So, what I'm saying is
CNN put out that interview that journ
It's that journalist who interviews
Nazis and incelss. That's the one they
gave me. Remember her? What's her name?
Ellie Reeves. El Reeves. Ellie Reeves.
Who's this woman? El Reev. I like
her. I thought we had a good
conversation. This is that woman who
interviews incelss in their basement and
the Nazis. And this is who they gave to
me. There she is.
So I sat here for an hour with her.
She's like, "Comedy's right-wing now."
I'm like, "No, it's not." She goes,
"Name a big left-wing comedian." I'm
like, "Bill Burrow, John Melany, Chelsea
Handler, Trevor." No, they're all arena
acts. What are you talking about? Louis
CK, my friend. What do you mean left?
Like who's consistently been left of
center forever? And they're all arena
acts. As Ronnie Chang, I love both of
them. I think they're great. And I just
and not only because of the line, which
I respect Assan for, but I also like the
comedy.
Um, so this woman's out there talking
about that Hollywood's like comedy is
rightwing. She's like, "Don't you think
you're the new establishment?" I'm like,
"Yes, it's 22 intelligence agencies, the
entire permanent federal government,
every legacy media institution in the
Ivy League
verse
Theo." Yes, that's the new
establishment. But she made some points
and I made some points. Release it in
full.
And I respect if they do that. And if
they don't, what was I saying now? Where
was I before I got to this? So, I'm on
these news channels waiting to go on.
Cancel culture is being cancelled.
What's going on? The woke the woke the
woke
mob. Did the woke mob tie you to a
[__] tree and beat you with the
sensitivity stick? And I'm like, well, a
little
um and I just want to hear
Chamatha talk
about the chips being backtored through
Singapore companies to China. It's
really
interesting. I'm not saying that the
people are wrong in the cable news, but
you know, there's just a certain kind of
fun like boomer
angle. The woke libs are going to hate
this special. Woke losers are going to
hate it.
lot of pronouns going out the door when
this special it's just me talking about
my mother and stuff but I listen I I
grew up watching these networks I like
to I like to listen literally one of
them I was before I go on one of them
all all the guy goes he goes and they're
rape I swear to go he goes like this he
goes and they're raping people next
comedian Tim Dylan has a new special on
Netflix that woke people are going to
have a stroke about. Um, but so now as I
go to these release it as we go to these
release
it have the courage to release the full
interview. It'll do
well. She's like there's a comedian in
my neighborhood. I go I don't know
anyone who lives in your neighborhood.
Trust me. But I do think I know who she
was talking about. The point is this.
The point is
this. As I'm sitting in the in these
news things waiting to go on and promote
the special I'm your mother on Netflix.
They're talking about this case. This is
the big case of the week. Um this guy
that was sent to this prison and
everybody's up in arms about it and
people are very upset. So I'm trying to
get like the facts and I'm trying to
figure
out what exactly happened. 2019 wasn't
yesterday. So he was suspected in 2019.
Maybe he was [__] around in 2019 and
he turns his life
around. I don't know. I don't know what
he was
doing. I don't know. I'm I'm unaware you
podcasters don't have any of the
facts. Prize Picks is the best place to
turn your sports knowledge into cash.
With millions of members, Prize Picks
has made daily fantasy sports accessible
to all. You just pick more or less on at
least two players for a shot to win up
to 2,000 times your cash. Run your game
all season long on prize picks. I mean,
I love it. Cash in on the basketball
playoffs with prize picks. Don't miss
your last chance to add your favorite
players from the court to your prize
picks lineup. Whether it's points,
rebounds, assists, take your pick of
more or less for your shot to win up to
2,000 times your cash today. Turn your
playoff hot takes into tickets to
basketball's championship series.
Starting with the playin round, every
lineup you make on prize picks will
enter you in the takes two ticket sweep
stakes could which could get you and a
plus one VIP trip to the
ship. Prize picks is the best way to get
action on sports in more than 30 states
including California, Texas, and
Georgia. Every Tuesday, prize picks will
discount several projections on the
board, usually by 15% to 25%.
I love Taco
Tuesday. Today is Flex Friday. Make sure
you opt in and tap the check box in your
lineup builder to be eligible for
protected play. Choose squares from any
game on the board. If your lineup does
not win, you get your net losses back in
promo funds up to your promo limit as
soon as the lineup settles. How cool is
that?
Download the app today and use code TIM
to get $50
instantly when you play your first $5
lineup. That's code TIM to get $50
instantly after you play your first $5
lineup. Prize picks, run your game.
Prize picks, run your game. Prize picks,
run your
game. This is something the the Jeff
Bezos space flight this is it has it
itarkens back to the days of that
Imagine where the celebrities are
singing Imagine. I just wanna I w
to send a public service announcement
out
to celebrities in
general and more specifically the
Democratic party if they ever want to
win another election. And I'm not saying
all these people are Democrats. I don't
know what Katy Perry believes and
neither does she.
What I think we need to
do
stop everything is
doesn't have to
be
like this really
grotesque self
congratulatory thing that everybody's
doing where everyone if something's
important we'll
know if something matter matters will
will know
that when the Civil Rights Act passed,
it was
important and and it was known that it
was
important. Flying for 10 minutes out of
out of Earth's orbit while Chris Jenner
watches standing in the middle of the
desert isn't important. If you have to
tell
us how important something you did is,
it probably doesn't matter. And people
don't want to hear it. So, if the
Democratic Party ever wants to win
another election, they just have to stop
[__] with these people. You have to
stop
censoring these people who are out of
touch, who are on another planet,
literally.
literally have left the planet.
Literally, you cannot have these people
as advocates. this blue origin space
flight space tourism whether it's done
by Elon Musk or Jeff Bezos's
trillionaire wife or Katy Perry or or
Gail King or any of these people no
matter who does it it's ne as things on
earth get
worse space tourism is going to look
terrible it's not going to look good
that even for a few minutes that you are
telling people. We can get out of here.
We can leave the planet if we want to.
You have to stay and deal with the
sickness, the crime, the war, and the
death. We get to blast off in a
spaceship and then to land and tell
people that this really mattered, that
this was important, and that they should
thank you. The attitude these people had
when they landed in a spaceship was that
people should thank them for some
sacrifice they made. It was
crazy. Here's Katie Perry talking about
how space can affect change or what.
This is just again I don't even care
that they did it. I don't care. I'm not
offended that you went to
space. Jeff Bezos is a rich guy. This is
rich guy [__] in
2025. His [__] is like, I want to go to
space and I want to bring my friends
into space.
Life never changes that much from when
you are in ninth grade and you get
invited to a party and you're excited
about it because you're going to a
popular kid's house maybe has a big pool
or they're a jock or people like them
and you get excited. Life doesn't really
change that much. You got this rich
[__] Bezos's wife, and she's got her
huge tits blasting into space, and she's
got her friends and she can call them
and go, "Would you like to go on my
spaceship?" And they do that. And that's
all fine and good. That's all fine and
good. Don't number one, get the cameras
out. What are we doing? Get the cameras.
How cool would it be to be Nobody knows
how to do this, right?
You should be on the spaceships
secretly. We want to do We're gonna What
a story. What a [__] story. We went
to space last week. This whole idea that
you have to explain all the cool [__]
you do to people that can never even
dream of doing it and then wonder why
they all hate you is crazy. Just do it
quietly. be like, "How is there anything
cooler than just lying to your
significant other and go, I'm taking a
girls weekend and then showing the video
and go, we were in [__] space." Let
it leak out a year later. The gayest
thing in the world, not gay, that's
fine, but gay in the way of like
annoying and like, you know, whatever,
is to tell people what you did right
after you did it and try to make it seem
important. the coolest people in the
world keep things kind of close to the
vest. That's what celebrities used to
do. Now they tell you everything they're
doing. I think these celebrities think
they can talk about everything
uh that isn't illegal because a lot of
them have done they've probably been
party to so much illegal [__] and these
crazy parties before cell phones and God
only knows what people were doing. Like
they'd find some drifter and start
barbecuing it in the back of some
Hollywood Hills house. That they can't
talk about. They can't talk about many
of them on the Epstein list. But they
really want to tell you about space as
if you give a [__] You're supposed to
be working your second shift at a
supermarket and on your busted screen
iPhone watch Katy Perry, this out of
touch [__] talk about the sacrifice
and how important it was that she went
up to space for 15
minutes. Nobody knows how to be cool
anymore. It's one of the most
disappointing things about our society.
All these rich people and these
celebrities have showed their ass.
That's why they can't influence anything
anymore. That's why nobody looks up to
them. It's the death nail of celebrity
culture because we've realized how much
they suck. What? Play this, please. We
can um see the unity um that we modeled
and replicate that and understand that
we weren't just taking up space, we were
making space. Okay, stop it for a
minute. All they did was sit in a
thing. That's literally all these
[__] did was sit in a a little pod
and then float. They did nothing. They
didn't do a goddamn thing. They didn't
build the [__] rocket. They didn't
like these [__] got invited on a
trip. You got invited to your friend's
lakehouse and you had fun going tubing
and eating s'mores. You don't go
back to your other friends on the block
and say they're like, "Yo, you got back
from Bill's Lakehouse. Yeah, it was an
important moment.
We went tubing and ate s'mores. We
stayed up till 3:00 a.m. And we realized
that the unity that we built, it's like
people be like, "Dude, you [__] suck.
What is wrong with
you? They're trying to make you believe
that these pointless rich
adventures mean something to your shitty
life." Continue for the future. And um
for me, like Gail said, this wasn't a
ride. It wasn't a destination. It was a
ride. It was a journey and it was a
supernatural one. It's a literal ride.
It's legitimately a ride. You can't say
it wasn't a
ride. It's It was That was all it was.
You didn't discover any What What are
your findings, [__] What did you
discover?
Do you have what are you you have
anything to tell us about the [__]
ozone layer? It was literally a run. Get
the video of them up floating these
[__]
Look at this. I've seen it. I want to
see it myself. Does this look
scientific?
[Music]
And if that exploded right then and
there. If that exploded. I mean, look at
Katy Perry. I mean, look at Katie Perry.
If that pod or that little module
exploded right
there, but we still got that video, it
would be I mean, this is
crazy. But again, you're just doing rich
[__] That's all you're doing. This is
the problem with that Imagine video
during co when they were all standing in
like mansions going,
"Imagine the people." And people are
like, "Bitch, I live in a in a
[__] tiny apartment and you're
standing in the back of your yard and
you don't care about a quarantine and
you don't care that you can't work and
you don't care that your business got
shut down cuz you're like walking around
your yard picking fruit and singing,"
imagine, "But we're all [__]
here. These people should have just
quietly done this." How cool. Because by
the way, no one would hate you. You
would have went to space. It would have
been fun. And then no one would have
hated you. Everyone hates you now.
Everyone hates you. All you had to do
was keep your mouth shut about a cool
rich thing you
did while the economy, by the way, the
economy is crumbling.
I mean, I don't I don't know how else to
say it. These [__] are floating in
outer
space and trying to tell people that
they did it for them. They like did it
for the common good because I don't
know. Did anyone by the way this isn't
one of these things where like we're
like women women have gone to space.
Real space. [__] have been in space.
[__] have died in space. Real women
astronauts have gone to space who've
been to space. Wasn't a [__] in a space
station who just got back. She was stuck
up there for months, months and months.
This [__] was in space six minutes or
something, Katy Perry. And she's acting
like she's the first slit to go to
space. You are not the first slit in
space. Slits have been going to space. I
don't get it. It's the craziest thing in
the world. There's been women have been
in space. They've been in space. They've
been stuck in space
stations. And this this person is acting
like it's a big [__] deal cuz she's
famous. That's her whole thing. She's
like, "No, no, no. You don't
understand. I have a life worth losing."
And I went, "That's her whole point
here. No, no, no, no, no. did this
because it was a little bit of a risk
and I have a life that's it it would
sucks if I die. If you people die, who
cares? But if I die, I lose out on cool
[__] I'm loaded. I'm rich and I'm
famous and and my life has value. So if
so, it's crazy to me and and the
reaction of this has just been now
they're now they are hatish. She they'll
always be hated for this. Does it are
there any other quotes from these ladies
before we before we move on?
Anybody else speak?
Wow. Gosh, that's good. Just Katie's
face says it all right there.
[Applause]
It's an allwoman crew. Oh, was this the
first time it was just all women? Is
that what they're trying to say? It was
the first allwoman crew of people that
are not they're not astronauts. They
know nothing about anything. And they
were like, "By the way, could there be a
word? Who went? Get up the names of the
people who
went." Okay, let's see who is
there. Gail King, Aisha Bo, Kerianne
Flynn. Are any of them astronauts? Who
are they?
Okay, hold on. The flights roster seems
to have been assembled with an energy of
American girl a girl doll
collection. Pop star Katy Perry,
journalist Gail King, aerospace engineer
Aisha Bo. Okay, one person. Feminist
activist Amanda Nan great. I'm sure they
need her on other planets. Film producer
and Lauren
Sanchez. Kerianne Flynn, the film
producer and Lauren Sanchez. So there
was one person who deserved to be there
and that was the aerospace aerospace
engineer Aisha
Bo. Everybody
else is a guest and even she was a guest
aerospace engineer. She's not an
astronaut per se. So who
cares? Nobody can do anything good. What
if we started sending MS13 to
space instead of to El Salvador? Like,
just send them to
space to show
them what we can
do. Just send them up there. What if it
was those tattooed guys floating around
like that instead of Katy Perry and Gail
King? if it was just tattooed
MS-13 gang members floating around in
space. I don't know if this guy should
have been deported or not. I don't know.
Someone asked me if I wanted to go to
that Al Salvador and prison and do
interviews. They're like, "They'll allow
me. I think they'll allow me to like go
to the
prison and do
interviews. This is what I've been told.
I'm not going to do it."
I think that guy Bouquet maybe I don't
know maybe he'll allow me to go down
there and um do a show for
them. Do a I've never done a show in a
prison. It's something I've wanted to
do. I could do a show
for gang members that were deported from
America who was sent to that
prison and I could go down there and do
a show. But a lot of them it's probably
English is not their first language.
So, we're going to run into
that. You're going to run into that
problem. Watch the new special I'm your
mother on Netflix if you can. I
appreciate it. Release the full
interview CNN. Come on. Do the right
thing. Do the right thing. Be the good.
Show people that you are not editing
people that you are not lying, that you
believe in journalistic integrity. Put
the interview out. I sat down for a good
faith
conversation that lasted an hour and you
should have the decency to you can edit
sound, you can edit some shots,
whatever obviously, but the bulk of that
interview, the entirety of our
conversation, anything that was on
camera should be released
online.
Otherwise, I don't think people are
going to I mean, I'm going to keep
talking about this fact. I'm going to
tell everyone I know and maybe you go,
"Oh, who cares who you know?" Well,
maybe, but maybe not. I'm going to keep
talking about the fact that no one
should go on this network and and maybe
that doesn't matter. Maybe you don't
care, and that's fine. But I'll tell you
right now, it's not the right thing to
do to bring someone in and talk to them
for an hour and then edit it down
without I understand if you have to put
10 minutes on on on um TV, but you
should put the entire thing on the
internet. The entire thing should go on
the internet. all your questions about
Joe Rogan's comedy club, about comedy,
about entertainment, about podcasts,
about politicians doing podcasts. That
hour that we discussed why podcasts are
popular, all of the answers should be
available on the internet for people to
see. It would be terrible if people
started tweeting at CNN to release the
full interview. It would be horrible.
I'd never want something like that to
happen, but it might be interesting and
it maybe
should. That maybe should happen. And
there's people that are going to watch
the interview and not agree with certain
things I've said. I think she made a few
good points. I made a few good points.
Put the [__] interview out. It's not
cool to do anything less than that.
Well, um, I'll be back next week. We're
doing Rogan tomorrow. I wasn't even
going to do this one this week because
I've been talking so much. I'm sick of
myself. You're sick of me. I get it.
Listen to the All-In podcast with some
really fun guys. We had a great time.
Listen to Tiger Belly with the great
Bobby Lee. Joe Rogan Experience
tomorrow. And uh, I get it. It's enough
already of me. I've had enough of me. I
hate promoting. I hate going all over
the place. I'm gonna quiet up. I'm gonna
quiet down in a week. Let's just again
focus on humbling love on the spectrum.
Let's humble love on the
spectrum.
Okay. Little.